本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
好了  同学们
All right, class.
这些成绩单会让你们知道
These progress reports will let you know
自己在语文学习上的进步如何
how you're doing in English so far,
我对你们很多同学可都是很口下留德地用了“进步”这个词哟
and for many of you I use the word "progress" loosely.
让我得个A吧  让我得个A吧
Please let it be an "A".Please let it be an "A".
让我得个C吧  让我得个C吧
Please let it be a "C". Please let it be a "C".
格尔金先生  对于你来说  快餐事业可谓蒸蒸日上
Mr. Gerkin, the fast food industry is booming
也有着远大前程可以期待呢
and offers a bright future.
好极了
This is great.
糟透了
This is terrible.
我拿了一个B耶
I got a "B".
我也是啊
So did I.
我都不敢相信自己得了一个真正的B
I can't believe I got a real "B".
跟什么相比啊
As opposed to what?
本来以为是D啊  这样我只要在上面再加个D
A "D" that I have to write another "D" on top of
就可以让它看起来像B了
to make it look like a "B".
丁沃尔老师
Mr. Dingwall,
我能问您一个小问题吗
can I ask you a quick question?
你已经问了  再见
You just did. Goodbye.
不是的  我想问的是关于我的成绩
No, actually it's about my grade.
我本来期待能得到A的
I was kind of expecting an "A".
在说A啊
"A"
这正好就是“烦人”这个单词的首写字母
the same letter that begins the words "annoying"
也是“再见”的首写字母
and "adios."
难道您就不能稍微解释下为什么我只得到B吗
Can you just explain to me why I got a "B"?
语文可是我的最强科目啊
English is my best subject.
虽然我的数学和科学课老师可能要为此争一争
Although my math and science teachers would argue with that.
再教你个夏威夷的再见 “阿喽哈”也是A打头哦
Here's another one-- aloha.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
Today's all burnt toast
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
Running late, and dad jokes
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
Has anybody seen my left shoe
■
翻译： 山鹰逢羽
我闭上双眼  咬口早餐
I close my eyes, take a bite
跳上车子  放声大笑
Grab a ride, laugh out loud
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
There it is up on the roof
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
I've been there, I've survived
所以听取我的建议
So just take my advice
■
校订  后期： WaitinZ
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, baby,
世界有很多疯狂无奈
Things are crazy
可是我知道你会有美好未来
But I know your future is bright
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, Baby
不要怀疑
There is no maybe
一切终会如你所愿
Eveything turns out all right
生活有悲有喜
Sure life is up and down
可是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
But trust me, it comes back all around
你会喜欢将来的你
You're gonna love who you turn out to be
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, Baby
查莉成长日记  第一季第十三集
Good Luck Charlie  S01E13  Teddy's Little Helper
小伙子  准备好去参加篮球赛了吗
Hey, ready for your basketball game?
我必须得去吗
Do I have to go?
我们一直都是输
All we ever do is lose.
那可不对啊
That is not true.
有时候你们是丧失资格
Sometimes you forfeit.
哦宝贝  乐观自信是很重要的
Oh, honey, it's important to think positive.
确实  你们已经连输了十一场
True, you've lost 11 games in a row
基本上在联赛里算是垫底了  不过嘛
and you're dead last in the league, but--
我也不知道想出什么好话来安慰你了
I don't know where I'm going with this.
坏消息  盖比
Bad news, Gabe.
我今天不能给你们比赛当教练了
I can't coach your game today.
刚接到一个紧急除害电话
Just got an emergency extermination call.
是什么大紧急事件呀
What's the big emergency?
瓢虫出没
Ladybug infestation.
好可爱
Aww.
那是  一只小瓢虫很讨喜
Oh, sure, one's cute.
成千上万那可就是极端恐怖的大灾难了
Thousands-- unspeakable horror.
那我看既然比赛没有教练
So I guess without a coach
我们今天就不用比了吧
we won't be able to play our game today.
喂  等一下  我可以当教练呀
Hey, wait a minute. I can coach.
哦呵呵  真是可爱的想法  亲爱的
That's cute, honey,
不过做教练这回事比你想像中可能要复杂一点点
but coaching's a little more complicated than you might think.
哎哟  亲爱的  我顶多也就跟你输的一样惨嘛
Oh, honey, I can lose just as good as you can.
我在说什么呀  我是不能去当教练
What am I saying? I can't coach.
我还得带查莉去上亲子联谊会呢
I have Mommy & Me with Charlie.
我可以带查莉去亲子会呀
I could take Charlie to Mommy & Me.
亲爱的  真是可爱的想法  不过亲子班这回事
Honey, that's cute, but Mommy & Me
比你想象中可能要复杂一点点
is a little more complicated than you might think.
其实  根本不复杂  你带她去参加就好了
Actually, it's really not. You go ahead and take her.
好了  亲爱的  看来你决心加入了
All right, honey, looks like you're in.
这是教练手册
Here's the playbook.
现在要你记全有点太强人所难
Now this might be a little over your head,
所以你只要尽力而为就可以了
so just do your best.
攻组是我们队  守组是其他的那些人
Xs are our team. Os are the other guys.
得了吧  攻组不是连输11场了吗
Okay, the xs have lost 11 games in a row, right?
说的对
Right.
我们这礼拜就转型防守吧
We're gonna be the os this week.
嘿嘿  小查莉  你的泰迪大姐姐又在录视频了
Hi, Charlie, it's your big sister Teddy here.
不然我是不是应该说自己是个大废材呢
Or should I say big failure Teddy?
我就是想让你看看我第一次拿到B分数后的有多么悲哀
I just wanted to show you how sad I look after I got my first "B".
而我就是想让你看看我第一次拿到B分数后有多开心
And I just want to show you how happy I look when I got my first "B".
喔哈哈
Whoo!
真抱歉让你看到这个
Sorry you had to see that.
我不应该得到B的
I do not deserve a "b".
我也是一样的感受啊
I felt the same way.
知道吗  我知道丁沃尔老师为何会给我一个差分
You know, I know why Dingwall gave me a bad grade.
他就是不喜欢我
He just doesn't like me.
要说  也真有可能
You know, that could be.
每次他跟你说话时那张脸都好像有人刚放了臭屁一样
Whenever he talks to you, he makes a face like somebody just cut one.
可这不公平啊
But it's not fair.
我从没放过屁  一直是格尔金在课堂上放屁的
I never cut one. It's always Gerkin.
那就算丁沃尔不喜欢你又怎么样  谁在乎这个呢
So what if Dingwall doesn't like you? Who cares?
我在乎呀  我可没尝过被人不喜欢的滋味呢
I care. No one's ever not liked me before.
不是我自夸  可是像我这种讨喜的人就是到哪都讨喜
I don't mean to be conceited, but likable people like me are liked.
这就是事实啊
It's just a fact.
只要你没那么自大就行
As long as you're not conceited.
我知道该怎么办了  我要让丁沃尔喜欢我
I know what I gotta do--get Dingwall to like me.
我知道我要做什么了  继续跳舞
I know what I gotta do-- more dancing.
我身上仍然充满了开心的能量呢
I still got some happy left in me.
要是我得了A  你可真要小心些了
You'd better watch out if I ever get an "A".
老爸  我回来了
Hey, dad.
回来啦  亲子会玩得怎么样啊
Hey, how was Mommy & Me?
真是了不起呀  那些师奶们可喜欢我了
It was awesome. The moms loved me.
我给她们讲笑话  逗她们开心
I told them some jokes, made them laugh,
又教她们怎么设置手机彩铃
taught them how to change their ringtones.
查莉玩得开心吗
Did Charlie have a good time?
我不知道  我都没顾得上看她
I don't know. I wasn't really watching her.
怎么样啊  情况有多糟
So? How bad was it?
真是糟呀
It was terrible.
对其他队伍而言真是太糟了
It was terrible for the other team
因为我们赢啦  赢喽  万岁
because we won! We won. Ooh ooh!
我不相信  盖比呢
I don't believe it. Where's Gabe?
他和队友们去吃冰激凌了
He went out for ice cream with the rest of the team,
在那之前他们把我一直举到车子上
right after they carried me to my car,
大声欢呼着“艾米  艾米”
chanting "Amy! Amy!"
真是的  小孩子就是大惊小怪的
Really, such a fuss.
对手是不是根本没来啊
Did the other team just not show up?
哎呀  他们当然来了
Oh, they showed up,
不过他们一定是后悔来了  被秒了
but they wish they hadn't. Kapow!
真是不可思议啊
That's amazing.
其实啊  根本没你想的那么难
Actually, it wasn't as hard as you thought.
我只不过告诉那些小男生就跑上场好好地玩耍吧
I just told the boys to go out there and have fun.
至少你用了那本教练手册吧
Did you at least use the playbook?
当然了
Absolutely.
那长凳太凉了  所以我把它用来当坐垫了
The bench was freezing, so I sat on it.
喂你好  哦  安吉啊
Hello. Hey, Angie.
不好意思啊  我没办法参加亲子会
Look, I'm sorry I couldn't make it to mommy & me--
你是想跟PJ说啊
you want to talk to p.J.?
我想他在家  稍等一下
I think he's here. Hang on a sec.
PJ
P.J.
怎么了
Yeah?
喂  哦是你啊  安子
Hello. Oh, hey, Ange.
对  和你们一起玩可有乐子了
Yeah, it was fun hanging out with you too.
太搞笑了
That's hilarious.
哦不是吧  你们当真吗
Oh no, you didn't.
你们能回避下么  这可是私人谈话
You guys mind? This is kinda personal.
对了  你有没注意到琳达的头发
By the way, did you see Linda's hair?
对吧
Right?
哟  这不是我的小赢家嘛
Hey, there's my winner.
老爸好
Hey, dad.
祝贺啊
Congratulations.
我是说  虽然是个狗屎运  对吧
I mean, obviously a fluke, right,
正好是你妈妈当教练的时候赢球了
happening when your mom was coaching?
不过你懂吧  我们应该可以在此基础上再接再厉
But you know what? I think we can build on this.
是啊是啊  老爸  我们需要谈谈
Yeah yeah. Dad, we need to talk.
聊什么呢
What about?
先坐吧
Have a seat.
行啊
Okay.
到底啥事
What's up?
这种事从来都不好开口
These things are never easy.
哪种事啊
What things?
听着  全队开了个讨论会
Look, the team talked things over
我们认为这样对所有人都最有利
and we think it's in everyone's best interest
就是说我们若在教练人员上做一些调整
if we make some changes involving the coaching staff.
教练人员  我不就是嘛
The coaching staff? I'm the coaching staff.
现在是啊
Yeah.
喂  等一下
Oh, wait a minute.
你是来炒我鱿鱼的么
Are you firing me?
也不想想我为球队付出了多少心血
After everything I've done for this team?
我们衷心祝福你万事如意
We wish you the best.
喂  得了吧
Oh, come on.
喂  不可能吧
喂  再给我个机会吧
Hey, give me another chance.
我可以扭转局面的
I can turn this thing around.
我觉得已经没必要再谈了
I think we're done here.
哦  老爸
Oh, dad,
你能把妈妈叫进来吗  我有些好消息要告诉她
would you send mom in? I have some good news for her.
好啊  D老师
Hey, Mr. "D".
这点小意思请笑纳
Got a little present for you--
是很好吃的自制巧克力饼干  因为啊
some yummy homemade brownies, just 'cause.
学校有关行政条例禁止教师接受任何形式的礼物
School district policy prohibits me from receiving gifts
就是为了以防如此情形发生
which, judging by these, does not appear to be a tragedy.
那个  我只是觉得可能你也跟我一样有口好牙
Well, I thought you might have a sweet tooth like me--
不就是我们又多了个共同点吗
just one more thing we have in common,
我是说  除了我们的种族来源之外
I mean, besides our ethnic heritage.
这话题不错
This should be good.
丁沃尔是一个苏格兰姓氏  就像邓肯一样呀
Dingwall is a scottish name, like Duncan.
我查了你的家族纹章
I looked up your family crest.
你知道那是两只飞翔的鹰吗
Did you know that it's two eagles in flight?
邓肯小姐  还是言归正传吧
Miss Duncan, let's cut to the chase.
你是为了分数来的  对吗
You're here about your grade, right?
你还真是位直白的苏格兰汉子啊
You are one sharp scottish cookie.
问题出在你的口头读书报告上
The issue is your oral book reports.
我做得很努力呀
I work very hard on those.
你表达得很枯燥无味
They're lifeless and dry,
这就是我的意见
and that's coming from me.
那好  我可以让它更活泼一些的
Okay, so I'll jazz them up.
你应该找个法子让你读的书更生动起来
Find a way to make the book come alive.
专心去做  而不是来拍老师的马屁
Put your energy into that instead of kissing up to your teacher,
这会让我觉得你很浅薄无礼  还有
which I find shallow, insulting and--
可爱死了
adorable!
啥
What?
甜心  好了  我们要走了
Honey, come on, let's go.
这  这  这是谁啊
Who-- who-- who is that?
这是哪家的小可爱啊
Who is that?
那是我妈妈和我妹妹查莉
That's my mom and my sister Charlie.
你是不是史上最漂亮的小宝贝啊
Aren't you the cutest baby ever?
我们很愿意这样想
We like to think so.
你长的真像你妈妈呀
And you look just like your mommy.
如果你是想恭维我是史上最漂亮的妈咪
If you're saying I'm the cutest mommy ever,
那我也接受
I accept.
泰迪亲爱的  我都不知道你还有个小妹妹呢
Teddy dear, I had no idea you had a baby sister.
叫我泰迪  还亲爱的
Teddy? Dear?
是谁啊  是谁啊
Who is that? Who is that?
这怪胎从哪里来的
Who is that?
你在干啥呢
What are you doing?
观看我的书呀
I'm watching my book.
是读书报告的作业吗
For your book report?
对呀
That's right.
你应该说是读书而不是观看呀
Aren't you supposed to, oh, I don't know, read your book?
泰迪  学着点吧
Teddy, get with it.
现在哪个孩子还会去读书呀  你真老套的上学方式
Kids don't read anymore. You're so old school.
那你要是不好好读书  等你变老了
And if you don't read your book, you're gonna be
你就还得继续上学
old and still going to school.
哪惹你啦
Hey.
对不起  我烦着呢
Sorry. I'm just a little upset
因为我和丁沃尔老师的谈话
about my conversation with Mr. Dingwall.
他正在训我说我有多无聊
He was telling me how boring I was,
然后查莉进来了  他就像圣诞树被点亮一样蹦跶了起来
and then Charlie came in and he lit up like a Christmas tree.
你看  这不是有答案了嘛
Well, there's your answer.
什么的答案啊
To what?
怎么拿到A呗
To getting an "a".
你应该穿得像个宝宝一样去做讲演报告
You should do your presentation dressed up like a baby.
你这么一说  我倒是有个更好的主意了
You know what? I might have a better idea.
我是很想听
And I'd love to hear it,
不过最后一个莫希干人刚刚把衣服给脱了
but the last of the Mohicans just took off his shirt.
（注：美国小说《最后的莫希干人》）
盖比啊
Gabe.
喂  亲爱的  你会来给盖比的篮球比赛助威吗
Hey, honey, you coming to Gabe's basketball game?
为什么要去啊
What for?
因为你是他爹呗
Because you're his father.
要不然他也可以把我这个头衔给炒了呀
Or has he fired me from that too?
你还在为教练这事不高兴啊
You're still upset about this coaching thing?
当然不是了
Of course not.
虽然根据丹佛市青少年篮球协会的正式行文条例
Although according to the by-laws of the Denver junior
第十七条第九款规定
basketball association, article 17, section 9,
篮球队并不允许随意通过投票更换教练
the team is not allowed to take a vote and replace me,
但我不计较这些
but I've let it go.
那很好
Good.
哎呀
Oh.
你好  老爸
Hi, dad.
盖比
Gabe.
真是尴尬
This is awkward.
我没想到会在这里见到你
I didn't expect to see you here.
这是我家耶
In my home?
盖比亲爱的
Gabe, honey,
你是不是有话要跟爸爸讲啊
Is there something you would like to say to your father?
是呀
Yeah.
爸  那哨子我们要用
Dad, I'm gonna need the whistle.
哎呀  安吉  你怎么来了
Hey, ange. What are you doing here?
今天是女友出游夜呀
It's girls' night out.
哎呀  你开玩笑的吧  今晚我真的不方便去
Oh, you're kidding. Tonight's not good for me.
其实我是来接PJ的
Actually, I'm here to pick up p.J.
哟  还好吗  女同胞
What's up, girlfriend?
唔啦啦  唔啦啦
Ooh ooh!
你跟那些师奶们出去玩吗
Are you going out with the moms?
对呀  去吃些小菜
Yeah, gonna have some appetizers,
也可能唱唱卡拉OK什么的  尽量放松一下
maybe do a little karaoke, just let our hair down.
其实  珍妮还借了言情片的碟子
Actually, Jeannie rented a chick flick,
所以我们决定去她家玩
so we're gonna hang at her place.
言情片
A chick flick?
我一定要去看
I'm good to go.
晚上别等我了
Don't wait up.
晕  这可真碜的慌
Okay, that's just weird.
才怪  真让人磕碜的是我都给那些孩子当了一季半教练了
No, what's weird is that I coach those kids for half a season and--
得了  看开点吧  老公
Oh, let it go, Bob.
你在场上玩的开心吗  孩子
Are you having fun out there, kiddo?
老妈  难道你看不到计分板吗
Mom, can you not see the scoreboard?
比分是44比12耶  我们输惨了
It's 44-12. We're getting creamed.
盖比  你过来一下
Gabe, over here now.
怎么了
What?
我们根本不该炒了你爸
We never should have fired your dad.
那不是你出的主意吗
It was your idea.
老兄  我当时只想吃冰淇凌而已
Dude, I was hopped up on ice cream.
现在说不是太晚了么
Well, it's too late now.
也许还不晚
Or is it?
你知道自己该做什么了吧
You know what you gotta do.
你是什么意思
What are you saying?
我是说该是时候卷起裙角去炒了你老妈了
I'm saying it's time to hike up your skirt and fire your mom.
妈妈呀  我们得谈谈
Hey, mom, we need to talk.
当然可以了  你想说什么呢  宝贝
Sure. What's on your mind, honey?
这种事一向很难开口
These things are never easy.
你要炒了我  对吧
You're firing me, aren't you?
对
Yep.
也行  至少我们其中有一个人不会尝到失败的滋味
Well, at least one of us is undefeated.
祝你们好运了  输家们
Good luck, losers.
嘿  爸爸  老伙计  还好吗
Hey, dad, old pal, what's goin' on?
我来猜一下哈
Let me guess--
快乐教练不再管用了
coach "fun" didn't work out,
所以你爬回来找你爹
so now you're crawling back to dad.
那么你知道不  也许我已经看开不想管了
Well, you know what? Maybe I've moved on.
行啊  我去问尼克的爸爸好了
Fine. I'll go ask Nick's dad.
别别别  我来做  我会做
No no no. I'll do it. I'll do it.
男人们  兄弟们  过来吧  围成圈
Guys, men, come on, gather round.
现在听好了
Listen up. All right.
我们要团结起来拧成绳
We're gonna pull together.
我们要真正像一个团队那样去打比赛
We're gonna play as a team.
我们要付出所有努力
And we're gonna give it our all.
那样就能赢了吗
And then we'll win?
想得美
Not a chance.
不过至少我们可以
But here's what we can do--
上场好好打比赛  虽败犹荣
we can go out there and we can lose with dignity.
虽败犹荣  虽败犹荣
Lose with dignity! Lose with dignity!
耶
Yeah!
喂  伙计们
Hey, guys,
都回来  现在才半场呀
come on back. It's only halftime.
乔治·奥威尔所著的《动物农场》
"Animal farm" by George orwell.
《动物农场》这本书描绘了
"Animal farm" is a story about what happens
一些很理想化的动物们怎样从邪恶的人类主人手里
when idealistic animals take control of their farm
夺取农场控制权的故事
from the evil human owners.
没劲
Oof.
现在我要给大家介绍这些动物们
Now I'd like to introduce you to some of the animals.
来见见小猪雪球吧
Meet snowball the pig.
原来小查莉扮猪猪哦
Charlie's a pig.
我要兴奋得上天堂了
I've died and gone to heaven.
雪球  跟大家介绍一下自己吧
Snowball, tell us about yourself.
哦  我心肠特别好
Oh, I'm good-hearted
我相信动物社会应该各生物平等
and I believe that all animals should be treated fairly
并且共同分享财产
and share their property equally.
谢谢你  雪球
Thanks, snowball.
该让你回农场去啦
Time to get back to the farm.
再见  雪球
Bye, snowball.
再见
Bye.
但是农场还有很多麻烦事呢
But all is not well on the farm,
因为现在要出现的是
because here comes--
他就是领袖猪  拿破仑
Napoleon, the conqueror pig.
我是麻烦制造者
I am a troublemaker.
我告诉其中一些动物  他们比别的动物更优越
I tell some of the animals they're better than others.
对  我就是坏猪一头
That's right, I'm a bad pig.
照了照了照了
Oh oh oh.
我要把这张做成新的手机屏保
That is my new screen saver.
不过幸好  山羊茉莉
But thankfully, Muriel the goat
可以用她智慧的言语平息事件
calms things down with some of her words of wisdom.
出来吧  茉莉
Come on, Muriel.
我去看看她被什么绊住了
I'm gonna see what's keeping her.
在这儿拖什么拖哪
What's the hold up?
查莉好像是胀气老放屁
Charlie's kinda gassy.
搞不好是我们刚才在小馆子喂她吃的炸鱼条有问题
Might be those fish sticks we fed her in the cafeteria.
现在我自己也觉得肚子不对劲儿了
They're talking back to me too.
好了  我最好赶快弄完这个报告
Okay, I'd better wrap things up.
来吧  我抱抱  乖啊乖啊
Come here. Come here. Yes yes yes.
乖宝宝  不哭哈
All right. Okay.
现在出场的是讲话很快的山羊茉莉
And here is Muriel the fast-talking goat.
哟  孩子们
Hey, kids.
想知道我要说什么吗
Want to know what I have to say?
去看书吧
Read the book.
所以最后动物们都变得
So in the end the animals become
和他们推翻的人类一样败坏了
just as evil as the humans they overthrew.
你甚至分不清他们是动物还是人了
And now you can't tell the animals... from the humans.
谢谢大家
Thank you, everyone.
精彩啊  邓肯小姐
Bravo, Miss Duncan.
你的讲演使书本变得生动了
You made the book come alive,
真是史上最可爱的报告呀
and in the most adorable way.
我  我  我很抱歉
I'm-- I'm-- I'm so sorry.
艾薇  快来帮我
Ivy, help.
天  她把鱼条吐出来了
Oh, here come the sticks.
呃  现在这里闻起来很像动物农场了
Well, now it smells like an animal farm.
爸妈  我回来了
Hey, mom. Hey, dad.
回来啦  图书馆的故事会好玩吗
Hey, how was story time at the library?
还好啦  我们读了《大家一起来便便》那本书
It was okay. We read "Everybody Poops."
基本上书名就已经把故事结尾给剧透了
The title kind of gives away the ending.
小查莉玩的高兴吗
Did Charlie have fun?
我不知道  我没和她坐在一起
I don't know. We didn't sit together.
还有我马上又得出门
Anyway, I'm gonna be taking off again soon.
又要和师奶们一起出去逛哦
Going out with the moms again?
不是的  我对那个已经腻了
No no, I'm done with that.
幸好你还有腻的一天
I'm glad you're over it.
我也觉得
Me too.
也不知我当时怎么想的
What was I thinking?
我和那堆三十多岁的女人能有什么好聊的啊
What do I have in common with a bunch of women in their 30s?
老爸老妈  这位是玛姬
Mom, dad, this is Marge,
是图书馆的故事奶奶
the story lady from the library.
我们要一起去喝茶
We're going to tea.
你们昨天报告的成绩已经出来了
These are your grades on yesterday's final presentations.
格尔金先生  你戴发网一定很合适
Mr. gerkin, fit yourself with a hairnet.
（注：快餐店服饰卫生要求）
温兹小姐的
Miss Wentz.
哎呀我的天
Oh my gosh.
邓肯小姐  给你成绩单
Miss Duncan, your grade
还有我的衣服干洗账单
and my dry-cleaning bill.
哎呀我的天
Oh my gosh.
一连两次得了B
Two "B"s in a row?
要是我妈开始指望上了怎么办
What if my mom starts to expect this?
我最好想办法把这分数改成D
I'd better turn this into a "d".
丁沃尔老师
Mr. Dingwall.
什么事
Yes?
我只想谢谢你给了我A
I just wanted to say thank you for my "A".
你应得的  因为你表现出了创造力
You earned it, for creativity,
想象力和独特风格  做的不错
imagination and style. Nicely done.
谢谢
Thank you.
现在你就当那铃声是火警
Now pretend that bell was a fire alarm
已经火烧眉毛了  你就赶紧冲出去吧
and the flames are upon us.
就一句话
Just one more thing.
你知道吗  我有个傻不拉叽的想法
You know, I had this crazy idea
你对我这么严格是不是
that the reason you were being so tough on me
因为你不喜欢我啊
was because you didn't like me.
我想的挺傻的  对吧
It's crazy, right?
因为你肯定喜欢我的  对吧
Because obviously you like me, right?
泰迪啊
Teddy,
你的人生中不可能遇见谁都一定会喜欢你
not everyone in your life is going to like you,
而原因也不一定和你自己有关
and the reason may have nothing to do with you.
这并不意味着你做人失败
Doesn't mean you've failed.
只是表明你是个人  懂吗
Just means you're human. Okay?
懂了
Okay.
可是你从来没真正说过喜欢我
But, you know, you never actually said if you like me--
我走就是
okay.
好啦  要是您喜欢我  就什么也别说就行了
Okay, if you like me, don't say a word.
再见
Goodbye.
天杀的
Ugh!
好啦  小查莉  再也不给你吃炸鱼条了
Well, Charlie, no more fish sticks for you.
不过还是要谢谢你帮我度过丁沃尔老师那关
But thanks for all your help with Mr. Dingwall.
我得了个A  都是你的功劳耶  唔啦啦
Because of you I got an "a". Whoo!
我也学到了不是每个人都一定会喜欢我
And I learned that not everyone is going to like me,
我会适应的
and I'm okay with that.
我是在努力学着适应吧
I'm working on being okay with that.
不过我还是没死心
But just in case...
查莉  祝我好运吧
Wish me good luck, Charlie.
走走走  快点  快点
Go go go. Come on, come on.
你看见我那篮球队了吗
Have you seen the team?
他们从那边走了
They went that away.
快  快
Come on, come on.
你有看见
Have you seen the--?
这些邓肯家的
Duncans.
还没找到他们啊
Still can't find them?
没
No.
我把全城都搜了一遍了
And I've searched the entire city.
盖比这孩子的叛逆期到底要到什么时候结束啊
How was the so insanage done with Gabe
你晓得吧  我做教练时可从来没这问题
You know, when I was coaching we didn't have this problem.